means
sex
and you see these lines from birth
hey this is just outrageous
you are high school students
became completely fearless
but I'm a policeman
you can't fool me
I knew you wouldn't believe it
wait wait
I didn't say I don't believe it
according to you
some person took the glasses
Sona
called her to school and then pushed her off the roof
I think so
who why
I don't know
but I'm sure it wasn't suicide
suna used glasses
to blackmail people
she had many enemies
Is it possible that there are several pairs of glasses?
there have been several cases recently
similar to that one
what did your upstairs neighbor do?
and why am I saying all this
wait a minute
so you see the whole world in red yes
almost
that's why you wear sunglasses
Looks like life isn't all that easy for you
손나
what's wrong with you
fell asleep in class
so let's continue
The human genome consists of gonasomes and autosomes
gonasome is a pair of sex chromosomes
the remaining 22 pairs of autosomes are not involved in sex determination
everything is fine
what's nothing
she dozed off in class
and then woke up screaming
listen you look very tired
let's have fun this weekend
I can't why
if you don't want to go, just say so
I'm busy with what
I work where do you work
leave her alone
you're so curious
at the Mison Mison Hotel
Kim misung
I'm coming
I asked you to change it
you made a mistake again
I have no more strength
correct
sorry
I understand why you are so angry
in our dining room there is excellent chicken and delicious food
mison where are you from?
originally from Busan
I can't hear the accent at all
I worked a lot on it
why
I want to become an actress
actress
yes
I've already been invited to the casting
understandable
I wonder if he has a girlfriend
fell for the music teacher
he's handsome
I don't know from him
I'm sure just eat
room for a couple of hours
30,000 it was impossible to go to a normal place
what's the difference
we're not here for long anyway
thank you
I don't like it here
next time we'll go wherever you want
Kim Heeyoung bullied Tsuna
pushed her off the roof and ran away
where could she have gone?
we were unable to track her phone
or maybe
this is the korean teacher
pushed Son and committed suicide out of guilt
now this is the most logical version
The last time his phone picked up a signal was at school
but the body has not yet been found
in fact he was considered missing
and also according to the family
he was afraid of heights
It’s unlikely that he would have decided to push someone off the roof
but that's not certain
who was it
jiuk
what if Sona
this is not suicide
I don't want to rush to conclusions
but there's something fishy here
after Sona found the glasses
it's like she's been replaced
what's wrong with these glasses
they say
if you put them on
then you can see
who slept with whom
what
I think it's true
what do you have there
want to rent a room
yes
60,000
surprise
how I want to know
where does my friend work
you can't come here
you are underage
and you
an adult or something?
this is
illegal and what
there are guests now
I want to look at them, wait, I can’t
be quiet
a bit cramped
how inconvenient
don't fidget
why did you have to come here
I'm interested
it's so exciting
number please
206th
she 1 came
I've already seen it somewhere
yes
for my life
I have slept with many men
but
since you appeared
casual connections are no longer possible
fill the void in my heart
I'm scared
that I never
I can't get you
ㅎㅎ
I want to have sex
fool
you don't even have a boyfriend
this is now but before there was a lot
don't lie, you were just running after them
and at least once had a relationship
o
that I was right there
what is the woman wearing 1
works in the school administration remember
with glasses are you sure of it
looks different
but she can’t put on a wig and become a different person
hey keep it down
when henhab was little
her mother killed her father and ran away
I'll really believe it
you're crazy
I have a couple of questions
Sana had it too
line with
this is confidential
means
Sana's line leads
to your classmate Jiwon
no
I don’t know who Sona is related to
but he
not from our class
I'll definitely go crazy
do you think that Sona
pushed by the one with whom she is connected
yes
quite
maybe
Yesterday evening another murder occurred in the Kanam area
the suspect was detained near the crime scene
but by that time the victim had already died
at the time of arrest the offender stated
that now he is clean and never stopped grinning
this behavior may be a sign
mental disorder
there are several pairs of glasses
points
several
sorry
the melody is so beautiful
so I came in
that's great
know so much good music
what's the point
schoolchildren are indifferent to music
you're mison
remember me yes
you have a dream
guess
It’s unlikely that you want to spend your whole life working in acting school
I'm right yes
how did you do it
It’s clear from you that you have excellent control of your body, and that’s how it is
amazing
I'm good at it
looks like you are very talented yes
you're going home
yes
where is genjin
she has something to do
she left earlier
and you
not busy right now
you like deserted places
how did you find out about him
in high school I was a swimmer
I haven't trained for a long time
but sometimes I come here secretly
can you swim
no
everything is fine
I'm sorry
everything is ready, come on over
delicious
and here you can eat
until the legion is caught
Jin would be the first to run to make ramen
tell me
why did you jump
a
I understand if you don't want to say sorry
I
from birth
I see something
red lines
over people's heads
such
yeah
and I have
you believe me
why
why would you lie
I'm weird
mm
you're unusual
yes
and beautiful
but I'm ordinary
if I suddenly disappear
no one will notice
Genjin and I
we'll worry about you
nice
how many more times to repeat
it wasn't me
do I look like a fraud
detective consumin
look who's here juke hi
long time no see
why don't you answer calls
well
with a criminal it's too much
like for the first time
then you were just suspected
now you've become selective
we're done I can go yeah
pick up the phone
juke when you
none of your business
jiuk are you dating someone now?
you know me
yeah you don't start a relationship
but you always had someone
you're right to take a break
I like someone
but not in this regard and why
what kind of question
I'm interested in her as a person
I need a number
206 please
I've slept with many men in my life
yes I have slept with many men
that's right
I've had a lot of men
a lot
first
a small room was enough for me
where could I be
it seemed a little more and I would become a great actress
but over time
my ears hurt
I didn't care at all about the sounds from the neighboring rooms
the problem was me
I was afraid that I might be given away
even the slightest rustle
at school everything was the same
the thought scared me
that someone will hear
how I laugh
and then I found this place
here I feel free
one day I came across glasses
who opened a new world for me
from that moment I became
observe
everything is perfect here
in this room
my whole life
어
are you here
아
why suddenly such a place
memories came flooding back unexpectedly
did you miss me
아
아아
아아아
you're leaving
tomorrow at the same time
I extend
what number
ㅎㅎ
well how does it suit me
came
you're early today
Michonne
this is a melody
remember
we listened to it together that time
how did you get here
my lord
I have to confess something to you that
for my life
I've slept with a lot of people
men
what are you talking about yeah
for my life
I have slept with many men
since then
how did you appear
casual connections are no longer possible
fill the void in my heart
I'm scared
that I never
I can't get you
that's not normal
I've slept with many men in my life
you threw something at me
no
what's wrong with me
what's going on
somehow I don't feel good
I mixed something into the water
you will feel better
for my life
I've slept with a lot of people
men
but since you appeared
casual connections are no longer possible
fill the void in my heart
어
no my lord
wake up
아아아
아
please
아아아아아
아
아아아
for my life
I have slept with many men
with many
아
아아
what the hell is wrong with you
some crazy woman attacked me and took my clothes
where is this bastard where is she
how painful it is
call the police
there are glasses among the evidence
no
these people were connected
that woman only had 1 line
but it seems she didn’t lead to the music teacher
why do you work here
I can't say
you still won't understand
Do you think glasses are also involved in this matter?
looks like it
at school she always wore glasses
perhaps in those
which we were looking for
when she came to the hotel
then became with
another person
putting on glasses
she seems to be
felt special
Detective Khan
this can happen to anyone
that's why these glasses are dangerous
Detective Khan
this can happen to anyone
that's why these glasses are dangerous
I was going to tell you give it back
when I put on these glasses I realized
that you didn't lie to me
it made me shiver
I don't believe you
get rid of glasses
we have a case of rape of a minor
Have you had sexual intercourse before?
no
Well, why is she lying?
There's been so much going on at school lately
Detective Khan she's a virgin
you are now wearing glasses
would you like to have dinner with me?
I think we just gotta say
between the lines
what is real what is not
how are you so sure
still insecure by myself